<%= provide(:title, "Style Guide") %>

<div class="colored-block">
    <div class="header-shade">
        <div class="header">
            <div class="header__nav contain-to-grid">
                <nav class="top-bar" data-options="is_hover:false">
                    <ul>
                        <li class="name brand-logo"><h1><a href="#">CashAmerica</a></h1></li>
                        <li class="toggle-topbar"><a href="#"></a></li>
                    </ul>
                    <section>
                        <ul class="left">
                            <li class="has-dropdown">
                                <a href="#">Services</a>
                                <ul class="dropdown">
                                    <li>
                                        <a href="#">Pawn Loans</a>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <a href="#">Auto Title Loans</a>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <a href="#">Cash Advances</a>
                                    </li>
                                    <li>
                                        <a href="#">All Services</a>
                                    </li>
                                </ul>
                            </li>

                            <li>
                                <a href="#">Online Catalog</a>
                            </li>


                            <li>
                                <a href="#">Store Locator</a>
                            </li>
                        </ul>

                        <ul class="right header__your-store">
                            <li class="has-dropdown">
                                
                                <div class="your-store">
                                    <div class="your-store__store-address">
                                        
                                        <address class="store-address">
                                            <span class="your-store__label">Your Store</span>
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="org">Cash America Pawn - 12345 </span>
                                            </div>
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="street-address">12345 Chestertonfieldville Ave # 1234567 </span>
                                            </div>
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="locality">Chestertonfieldvilledale, EE 6543 </span>
                                            </div>
                                        </address>
                                    </div>
                                </div>


                                <ul class="dropdown store-address-list">
                                    <li>
                                        <address class="store-address">
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="org">Cash America Pawn - 12345 </span>
                                            </div>
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="street-address">12345 Chestertonfieldville Ave # 123 </span>
                                            </div>
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="locality">Chestertonfieldvilledale, EE 6543 </span>
                                            </div>
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="locality">Phone </span><span>123-123-1234</span>
                                            </div>
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="locality"><a href="#">Make this my store</a> </span>
                                            </div>
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="locality"><a href="#">Show on map</a> </span>
                                            </div>
                                        </address>
                                    </li>

                                    <li>
                                        <address class="store-address">
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="org">Cash America Pawn - 12345 </span>
                                            </div>
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="street-address">12345 12 1st St </span>
                                            </div>
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="locality">Azle, EE 6543 </span>
                                            </div>
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="locality">Phone </span><span>123-123-1234</span>
                                            </div>
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="locality"><a href="#">Make this my store</a> </span>
                                            </div>
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="locality"><a href="#">Show on map</a> </span>
                                            </div>
                                        </address>
                                    </li>

                                    <li>
                                        <address class="store-address">
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="org">Cash America Pawn - 12345 </span>
                                            </div>
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="street-address">12345 Chestertonfieldville Ave # 123 </span>
                                            </div>
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="locality">Chestertonfieldvilledale, EE 6543 </span>
                                            </div>
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="locality">Phone </span><span>123-123-1234</span>
                                            </div>
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="locality"><a href="#">Make this my store</a> </span>
                                            </div>
                                            <div>
                                                <span class="locality"><a href="#">Show on map</a> </span>
                                            </div>
                                        </address>
                                    </li>
                                </ul>
                            </li>
                        </ul>
                    </section>
                </nav>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
</div>




<div class="row">
    <div class="twelve columns">
        <h1>Heading h1</h1>
        <h2>Heading h2</h2>
        <h3>Heading h3</h3>
        <h4>Heading h4</h4>
        <h5>Heading h5</h5>
        <h6>Heading h6</h6>
        </div>

    </div>

